https://www.costlesslighting.com/privacy_policy_i41.html?osCsid=j77oaaho8fakck7c8fki56pqp0

Quote0 products
Your quote is empty!
LED Wall Pack LightsLED Canopy Lights
LED Security/Flood & L...
LED Corn Lights
LED Paddle Lights
Mounting Parts & Acces...
Step-Down Transformers
Indoor LED Lighting
LED Flat Panel & Cente...LED High Bay LightsLED Strip Lights
Food Processing Lumina...
LED Exit & Emergency L...LED Recessed Cans & Tr...LED Wrap Around Ceilin...
LED Under Cabinets
LED Bulbs & TubesLED Ceiling Rounds & S...LED Vapor Tight Lights
Smoke & Carbon Monoxid...
Receptacles
Lutron Wireless Dimmin...
Cover Plates
Smoke & Carbon Monoxid...
Statement of Privacy
Cost Less Lighting is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to Cost Less Lighting Web site and governs data collection and usage at all Cost Less Lighting sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the Cost Less Lighting Statement of Privacy. Cost Less Lighting is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Cost Less Lighting is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of Your Personal Information
As an E-commerce Web site, Cost Less Lighting collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by Cost Less Lighting is used solely for the purpose of billing your online purchases. Cost Less Lighting does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.
Cost Less Lighting encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Cost Less Lighting so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Cost Less Lighting Web site.
Use of Your Personal Information
Cost Less Lighting and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested. It is possible that Cost Less Lighting may also use personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Cost Less Lighting and its affiliates. Cost Less Lighting may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Cost Less Lighting does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Cost Less Lighting may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
Cost Less Lighting does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Cost Less Lighting may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Contractor Lighting or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Cost Less Lighting including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Cost Less Lighting or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Contractor Lighting or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Cost Less Lighting abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control Your Personal Information
Cost Less Lighting offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may go notify us of your preferences by emailing infor@costlesslighting.com. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records.
You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Cost Less Lighting by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list
Security of Your Personal Information
Cost Less Lighting is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through a secure SSL encrypted Payment Service.
Changes to this Statement
Cost Less Lighting will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how Cost Less Lighting will use your personal information, Cost Less Lighting will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. Cost Less Lighting encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Cost Less Lighting is protecting your information.
Continue
About
Company Information
Privacy Policy
Terms Of Service
Announcements
FedEx Shipping Info
About
